Labor Relations Board Files 6103
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Labor Relations Board Files
1973-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center
6103
15 cubic feet
15 linear ft.
Case files.
The labor relations boards files are comprised of documents from federal and state boards of labor relations in the U.S., Puerto Rico, and Canada. They were collected by the Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives and formerly housed in the Center's Current Documents collections.
3461279
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 23, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 19, 2015
Scope and Contents
Records of decisions from various federal and state labor relations boards.
The agencies represented in this collection include the U.S. Conciliation Service, the U.S. Division of Management Relations Services, the New York Labor Relations Board, the Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board, the Puerto Rico Industrial Relations Board, the Connecticut State Board of Labor Relations, the Massachusetts Labor Relations Comission, the New Jersey Public Employee Relations Commission, the New York City Office of Labor Relations, and the Labour Relations Board of Canada.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Industrial relations -- New York (State) -- New York; Industrial relations -- New York (State); Industrial relations -- Massachusetts; Industrial relations -- Connecticut; Industrial relations -- Puerto Rico; Industrial relations -- Canada; Workers' compensation -- Pennsylvania; Canada Labour Relations Board.; Connecticut. State Board of Labor Relations.; Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives.; Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission.; New Jersey. Public Employment Relations Commission.; New York (N.Y.). Office of Labor Relations.; New York State Labor Relations Board.; Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board.; Puerto Rico. Labor Relations Board.; United States. Labor-Management Relations Services.; United States. Conciliation Service.
3461279
- New York Labor Relations Board - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board (Box 1)
  - New York Labor Relations Board Decisions - 5451 - 5499 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - New York City Office of Municipal, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - New York Labor Relations Board Decisions 4293-5451A (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - New York City Office of Municipal Relations, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - New York City Office of Municipal Relations, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - New York City Office of Municipal Relations, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - N.Y. Labor Relations Board Decisions 5500-5550 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - N.Y. Labor Relations Board Decisions 5551-5599 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - N.Y. Labor Relations Board - Decisions 5600-565B (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - N.Y. Labor Relations Board - Decisions 5651-5699 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - N.Y. Labor Relations Board Vol. 45 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - N.Y. Labor Relations Board Vol. 42, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - N.Y. Labor Relations Board Volume 40 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NYS Labor Relations Board No. 39 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - New York State Board of Labor Relations No. 38 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board Award 600-699 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board Award 700-800 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board Award 1700-1799 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board Award 3000-3999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board Award 4000-41000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board Award 41000-42000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board Award 42001-42100 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board Award 42101-42200 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board Award 42201-42300 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board - Puerto Rico Industrial Relations Board (Box 2)
  - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation - Award 42301-42400 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board Award 42401-42500 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board Award 42501-42600 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board Award 42601-42700 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Workmen's Compensation Board Award 42701-42800 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Puerto Rico Decisions - Industrial Relations Board P 1600-1699 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Puerto Rico Decisions - Industrial Relations Board P1700-1799 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Puerto Rico Decisions - Industrial Relations Board P1800-1899 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Puerto Rico Decisions - Industrial Relations Board P1900-1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Puerto Rico Industrial Relations Board - U.S. Conciliation Service (Box 3)
  - Puerto Rico Decisions - Industrial Relations Bd. P2000-2099 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Puerto Rico Industrial Relations Bd. Decisions P2000-2099 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Puerto Rico Industrial Relations Board P2200-2299 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Puerto Rico Industrial Relations Board Decisions PP1-100 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Puerto Rico, Supreme Court Decisions (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Puerto Rico Supreme Court Decisions (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Conciliation Service (Box 3, Folder 7)
- U.S. Division of Management Relations Service Decisions - Canada-Labor Relations Board (Box 4)
  - U.S. Division of Employee-Management Relations Services - Arbitration Services (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Division of Employee-Management Relations Services - Arbitration Decisions (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Division of Employee-Management Relations Services - Arbitration Decisions (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Division of Employee-Management Relations Services - Arbitration Decisions (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Canada "Conciliation Board Reports together with CLRB Reasons for Judgment (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Canada: Quebec Ministere Du Travail Tribunal D'Arbitrage 600 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Canada: Quebec Ministere Du Travail; Tribunal D'Arbitrage 700 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Canada: Quebec Ministere Du Travail Tribunal D'Arbitrage 1300-1399 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Canada: Quebec Ministere Du Travail Tribunal D'Arbitrage 1400-1499 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Canada: Quebec Ministere Du Travail Tribunal D'Arbitrage 1500-1599 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Canada: Quebec Ministere Du Travail Tribunal D'Arbitrage B.S. 1-100 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 510-550 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 550-560 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 560-570 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Canada-Labor Relations Board (Box 5)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 570-580, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 580-590, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 590-600, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 600-700 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 701-750 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 751-775 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 776-800 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board 801-900 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 900-1000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board 1000-1100 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Canada-Labor Relations Board (Box 6)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 1100-1200, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 1200-1300 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board 1300-1400 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 1400-1500 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 1500-1600 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 1600-1700 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Canada-Labor Relations Board - Connecticut State Board of Labor Relations (#1-999) (Box 7)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 1700-1800 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 1800-1900 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Quebec 1900-2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Reports of Boards of Conciliation (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Canadian Labor Relations Board Saskatchewan (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Conn. Board of Labor Relations Decisions 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Conn. Board of Labor Relations Decisions 11-20 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Conn. Board of Labor Relations Decisions 21-30 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Conn. Board of Labor Relations Decisions 31-40 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Conn. Board of Labor Relations Decisions 41-50 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Conn. Board of Labor Relations Decisions 51-60 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Conn. Board of Labor Relations Decisions 61-70 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No. 71-80 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No. 81-90 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No. 91-100 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No. 101-110 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.111-120 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.121-130 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.131-140 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.141-150 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.151-160 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.161-170 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.171-180 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.181-190 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.191-200 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.201-210 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.211-220 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.221-230 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.250-300 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.301-400 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.401-500 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.501-600 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.601-700 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Connecticut #704-925 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Connecticut State Board of Labor Relations Decisions no. 926-999 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Connecticut State Board of Labor Relations (#1000-2299) (Box 8)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.1000-1099 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.1100-1199 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.1200-1299 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.13000-1399 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.1400-1499 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.1500-1599 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.1600-1699 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.1700-1799 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.1800-1899 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.1900-1999 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.2000-2099 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.2100-2199 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.2200-2299 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Connecticut State Board of Labor Relations (#2300-2999) - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission (CR 1251-1300) (Box 9)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.2300-2399 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.2400-2499 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.2500-2599 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.2600-2699 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.2700-2799 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.2800-2899 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Connecticut Board of Labor Relations Decisions No.2900-2999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. UP1099-1268 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR981-1150 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR1201-1250 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR1251-1300 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions (Box 10)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR1301-1350 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR1351-1400 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR1401-1450 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR1451-1500 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR1501-1550 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR1551-1600 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR1601-1650 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR1651-1700 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR1701-1800 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR1801-1900 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR1901-1999 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. 2000-2099 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. 2100-2199 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions - Case Nos. CR2200-2299 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions (Box 11)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case No. CR2300-2400 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case No. CR2400-2499 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case No. CR2500-2599 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case No. CR2600-2699 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case No. CR2700-2799 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case No. CR2800-2899 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case No. CR2900-2999 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case No. CR3000- (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case No. CRC1-50 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case No. CR2300-2400 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case No. CRE1- (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case No. MCR1-99 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Decisions (Box 12)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case MCR 100-199 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case MCR 300-399 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case MCR 400-499 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case MUP (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case SCR (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case MCR 500-599 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case No. UP (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Board Decisions - Cases MCR 600-699 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Massachusetts Labor Relations Commission Case No. USE (Box 12, Folder 9)
- New Jersey Public Employee Relations Commission (1970-75) (Box 13)
  - New Jersey Public Employment Relations Commission Decisions Perc. #'s (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - New Jersey Public Employment Relations Commission E.D. #'s (Box 13, Folder 2)
- New York City Office of Labor Relations (1973-1974) (Box 14)
  - New York City Office of Labor Relations 1973 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - New York City Office of Labor Relations 1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- New York City Office of Labor Relations (1975-78) (Box 15)
  - New York City Office of Labor Relations 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - New York City Office of Labor Relations 1976 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - New York City Office of Labor Relations 1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)